<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>home on indigomarxist</title><link>https://indigomarxist.github.io/</link><description>Recent content in home on indigomarxist</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 20:10:11 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://indigomarxist.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Burn the Constitution</title><link>https://indigomarxist.github.io/posts/burn-the-constitution/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 20:10:11 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://indigomarxist.github.io/posts/burn-the-constitution/</guid><description>Burn the Constitution To emphasize the commonality of the 99 percent, to declare deep enmity of interest with the 1 percent, is to do exactly what the governments of the United States, and the wealthy elite allied to them-from the Founding Fathers to now-have tried their best to prevent. Madison feared a &amp;ldquo;majority faction&amp;rdquo; and hoped the new Constitution would control it. He and his colleagues began the Preamble to the Constitution with the words &amp;ldquo;We the people &amp;hellip;,&amp;rdquo; pretending that the new government stood for everyone, and hoping that this myth, accepted as fact, would ensure &amp;ldquo;domestic tranquility.</description></item><item><title>How to Torrent</title><link>https://indigomarxist.github.io/posts/how-to-torrent/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 20:08:20 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://indigomarxist.github.io/posts/how-to-torrent/</guid><description>How to torrent Why Bittorrent? Most popular filesharing method worldwide. Shares files in a web, instead of single uploader. Can find most movies, shows, music, and books, for free. Once seeded, impossible to take down. Get a VPN ISPs watch what you download. Hides your traffic from your ISP. Protects you using tunneling and encryption. Find a Torrent Client qBittorrent Deluge Flud (Android) Find a Torrent Search Engine Use Google Find a Media Player VLC Next steps Get a media server like Plex for a Netflix-like experience.</description></item><item><title>Nietzsche</title><link>https://indigomarxist.github.io/posts/nietzsche/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 20:04:55 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://indigomarxist.github.io/posts/nietzsche/</guid><description>Why Nietzsche is a terrible role model for the left Instead of writing up a longer, meandering argument against Nietzsche&amp;rsquo;s philosophy, I found that his quotations themselves make the strongest argument for why he makes a terrible role model for the left.
The core concepts of his philosophy, Masculine virtue and elitism, the Superman, Will to Power, worship of warrior heroes and militarism, Anti-democracy, Anti-Socialism, Reverence for hereditary Aristocracy (whether Teutonic, or Roman), Anti-feminism, Anti-Christianity / Buddism, Biological determinism, are shown through his quotes.</description></item><item><title>Why Torrents</title><link>https://indigomarxist.github.io/posts/why-torrents/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 20:03:31 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://indigomarxist.github.io/posts/why-torrents/</guid><description>Why Torrents are better than streaming servers as a self hosted solution. Instead of using plex or emby, consider using a dedicated torrent server, and torrent clients elsewhere.
Quality Streaming servers can never have the same quality as local music / video players. Video streaming servers like plex or emby, often have to transcode / convert the video to lower-quality formats. Native video players can handle x265. Audio streaming servers often can&amp;rsquo;t handle high quality formats like flac, whereas local media players can handle these easily.</description></item><item><title>Socialism Faq</title><link>https://indigomarxist.github.io/posts/socialism-faq/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 20:00:39 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://indigomarxist.github.io/posts/socialism-faq/</guid><description>Socialism FAQ The Bullshit asymmetry principle, or Brandolini&amp;rsquo;s law:
The amount of energy needed to refute bullshit is an order of magnitude bigger than to produce it.
Contents Socialism FAQ Didn&amp;rsquo;t communism fail? It works in theory but not in practice. What about human nature? Schools of thought On Ultra-leftism / Left-Communism Did economic planning work? Who would sweep the floors under communism? What about cooperatives? What about democracy?</description></item><item><title>about</title><link>https://indigomarxist.github.io/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://indigomarxist.github.io/about/</guid><description> a collection of essays, resources, and content with a focus on marxist thought and online independance. themed with</description></item></channel></rss>